Register of the Gottfried Haberler papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings III, 1925-1989, undated
  - "Kann sie die Weltwirtschaftskrise wiederholen?", 1987 (Box-folder 78: 14)
  - "Die Kauftkraft des Geldes und die Stabilisierung der Wirtschaft,", 1931 (Box-folder 78: 15)
  - "Konvertibilität der Währungen,", circa 1950s (Box-folder 78: 16)
  - "Die Konjunkturtheorie als Teil der westlichen Wirtschaftstheorie,", circa 1960s (Box-folder 78: 17)
  - "Die Konjunkturaussichten in den Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika,", 1953 (Box-folder 78: 18)
  - "Kritische Bemerkungen zu Schumpeters Geldtheorie,", 1925 (Box-folder 78: 19)
  - Lecture notes and syllabi, 1930-1957, undated (Box-folder 78: 20 - 80: 3)
  - "Less Developed Countries and International Economic Order,", 1977-1978 (Box-folder 80: 4)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - "Liberal and Illiberal Development Policy: 'Free Trade Like Honesty Still Remains the Best Policy',", 1985 (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - "The Liberal International Economic Order in Historical Perspective,", 1979 (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - "The Market for Foreign Exchange and the Stability of the Balance of Payments,", 1949 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - "Der Marshall-Plan für wirtschaftlichen wiederaufbau Europas und die Dollarknappheit,", 1949 (Box-folder 80: 9)
  - "Marxian Economics in Retrospect and Prospect,", 1965 (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - "Methods of Harmonizing Resources and the Demand for Resources in Western Countries," draft and published copy, 1958, 1985 (Box-folder 80: 11-12)
  - "Mise's Private Seminar,", 1961, 1981 (Box-folder 80: 13-14)
  - "Mit oder ohne Inflation? 'Aufbau, nicht Aufbau',", 1932 (Box-folder 80: 15)
  - "Modern Challenges to a Liberal International Economic Order: A Historical Perspective,", 1977
  - "Modernos ataques a un sistema económico internacional liberal: una perspectiva histórica,", 1979
  - "Monetary Equilibrium and the Price Level in a Progressive Economy: A Comment,", 1935 (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - "Monetary and Fiscal Policy for Economic Stability and Growth,", 1963, 1967 (Box-folder 80: 2-3)
  - "Money and the Business Cycle,", 1932 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - "Money in a Liberal Society,", circa 1950s (Box-folder 81: 6)
  - "Möglichkeiten der Arbeitsbeschaffung in Österreich,", undated (Box-folder 81: 7)
  - "Multiplier Effects of a Balanced Budget: Some Monetary Implications of Mr. Haavelmo's Paper,", 1946 (Box-folder 81: 8)
  - "Münzreform,", 1934 (Box-folder 81: 9)
  - "National Income, Savings, and Investment,", circa 1930s (Box-folder 81: 10)
  - Various newspaper articles, 1928-1933 (Box-folder 81: 11)
  - "Notes on Rational and Irrational Expectations,", 1980 (Box-folder 81: 12)
  - "Nurkse on Patterns of Trade and Development,", 1980 (Box-folder 81: 13)
  - "El Orden económico internacional viejo y neuvo,", 1978 (Box-folder 81: 14)
  - "Os Ciclos Econômicos e o Crescimento da Economica dos Estados Unidos depois da Segunda Guerra Mundial,", 1965 (Box-folder 81: 15)
  - "The Pigou Effect Once More,", 1952 (Box-folder 81: 16)
  - "The Political Economy of Regional or Continental Blocs,", 1943 (Box-folder 81: 17)
  - "Politiki eisodika kai plithorismos,", 1971 (Box-folder 81: 18)
  - "Population Pressure and Economic Policy in Developed and Under-Developed Countries,", 1960 (Box-folder 82: 1)
  - "Preferenzzölle und Meistbegünstigung in der Handelspolitik der Vereinigten Staaten,", 1930 (Box-folder 82: 2)
  - "The Present Economic Malaise,", 1979 (Box-folder 82: 3)
  - "The Present State of Economics and the New Tasks of Diplomacy,", circa 1962 (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - "The Problem of Stagflation,", 1976 (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - "Problemas de Conjunktura e de Política Ecônomica,", 1948 (Box-folder 82: 6)
  - "Probleme der internationalen Wirtschaftspolitik,", 1977 (Box-folder 82: 7)
  - "Probleme der Konjunktheorie,", 1933 (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - "Prospects for the Dollar Standard,", 1972 (Box-folder 82: 9)
  - "Protectionism or Freer Trade in Less Developed Countries,", 1969 (Box-folder 82: 10)
  - "Protecionismo Alfandegário,", 1947 (Box-folder 82: 11)
  - "Quota," Encyclopaedia Britannica entry, 1945 (Box-folder 82: 12)
  - "Real Cost, Money Cost and Comparative Advantage,", 1951 (Box-folder 82: 13)
  - "Das reale internationale Austauschverhältnis (Terms of Trade) und die wirtschaftliche Entwicklung,", 1958 (Box-folder 82: 14)
  - "Recovery Policies in Democratic Countries,", 1938 (Box-folder 82: 15)
  - "Reflections on Economics,", 1990 (Box-folder 82: 16)
  - "Reflections on the Economics of International Monetary Integration,", 1971 (Box-folder 82: 17)
  - "Reflections of the Future of the Bretton Woods System,", 1953 (Box-folder 82: 18)
  - "Reflections on Hayek's Business Cycle Theory,", 1986 (Box-folder 82: 19)
  - "Reflexiones sobre el Futuro del Sistema de Bretton Woods,", 1952 (Box-folder 83: 1)
  - "Regionaler Zollabbau genügt nicht,", 1963 (Box-folder 83: 2)
  - "Remarks Prepared for a Luncheon Address at the Institute for International Economics,", 1986 (Box-folder 83: 3)
  - "Reply to Harry G. Johnson's Comments,", undated (Box-folder 83: 4)
  - "Report to the Task Force on U.S. Balance of Payments Policies to the President Elect,", circa 1960s (Box-folder 83: 5)
  - "Response to Max Corden and Robert Findlay,", 1985 (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - "Saving, Investment, and Monetary Stability as Preconditions for Economic Development and Growth,", 1963 (Box-folder 83: 7)
  - "Schleichende Inflation und knappes Geld,", 1958 (Box-folder 83: 8)
  - "Schumpeter: Social Scientist,", 1951 (Box-folder 83: 9)
  - "Schumpeter's Capitalism, Socialism, and Democracy After Forty Years,", 1981 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - "Schumpter, Minestre de Finances,", 1950 (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - "Schumpeter's Theory of Interest,", 1951 (Box-folder 83: 12)
  - "Should Floating Continue?", 1989 (Box-folder 83: 13)
  - "Sind wir zu ewiger Inflation verdammt?", 1971 (Box-folder 83: 14)
  - "Der Sinn der Indexzahlen,", 1927 (Box-folder 83: 15)
  - "The Slowdown of the World Economy and the Problem of Stagflation,", 1984 (Box-folder 83: 16)
  - "Some Aspects of Convertability,", 1955 (Box-folder 83: 17)
  - "Some Comments on Mr. Kahn's Review of Prosperity and Depression,", 1938 (Box-folder 83: 18)
  - "Some Currently Suggested Explanations and Cures of Inflation,", 1976 (Box-folder 83: 19)
  - "Some Factors Affecting the Future of International Trade and International Economic Policy,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 83: 20)
  - "Some Observations on the Japanese American Economic Relations,", 1972 (Box-folder 83: 21)
  - "Some Remarks on Recent Discussions about the International Payments System,", 1965 (Box-folder 84: 1)
  - "Some Reminiscences,", 1976 (Box-folder 84: 2)
  - "Special Drawing Rights and World Inflation," with related notes and correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 84: 3-4)
  - "Stagflation: An Analysis of Its Causes and Cures,", 1977 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - "Der Stande und die nächste Zukunft der Konjekturforschung,", 1933 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - "The State and Prospects of the U.S. Economy,", 1961 (Box-folder 84: 7)
  - "The State of the World Economy: Global Balance Exchange Rates, and the World Debt,", 1989 (Box-folder 84: 8)
  - "The State of the World Economy and the International Monetary System,", 1978 (Box-folder 84: 9)
  - "Strategic Trade Policy and the New International Economics: A Critical Analysis,", 1989 (Box-folder 84: 10)
  - "Survey of Circumstances Affecting the Location of Production and International Trade as Analyzed in the Theoretical Literature,", 1976 (Box-folder 84: 11)
  - "A Survey of International Trade Theory,", 1955 (Box-folder 84: 12)
  - "Systematczna analiza teoryj cyklu gospodarczego,", 1935 (Box-folder 84: 13)
  - "Systematic Analysis of the Theories of the Business Cycle,", 1934 (Box-folder 84: 14)
  - "Terms of Trade and Economic Development,", 1961 (Box-folder 84: 15)
  - "Theoretical Reflections on the Trade of Scocialist Economies,", 1968 (Box-folder 84: 16)
  - "The Theory of Business Cycles as Part of Western Economic Theory,", circa 1950s (Box-folder 84: 17)
  - "The Theory of Comparative Cost, Once More,", 1929 (Box-folder 84: 18)
  - "Die Theorie der komparativen Kosten und ihre Auswertung für die Begründung des Freihandels,", 1930 (Box-folder 84: 19)
  - "Theory as a Tool of Policy,", 1983 (Box-folder 84: 20)
  - "Thoughts on Inflation: The Basic Forces,", 1975 (Box-folder 84: 21)
  - "The Trade Policies in the 1980s: Comments,", 1983 (Box-folder 84: 22)
  - "Two Conflicting View of the German Balance of Payments Predicament,", 1971 (Box-folder 85: 1)
  - "Two Essays on the Future of International Monetary Order,", 1974 (Box-folder 85: 2)
  - "Um das Gleichgewicht in der Weltwirtschaft,", 1961 (Box-folder 85: 3)
  - "The U.S. Balance of Payments: Freedom or Controls,", 1970 (Box-folder 85: 4)
  - "U.S. Balance of Payments Policies and International Monetary Reform: A Critical Analysis,", 1968 (Box-folder 85: 5)
  - "U.S. Balance of Payments Policy and the International Monetary System,", 1973 (Box-folder 85: 6)
  - "The U.S. Budget Deficit and the Strong Dollar,", 1989 (Box-folder 85: 7)
  - "Die Verschwendung als Wirtschaftsphilosophie,", undated (Box-folder 85: 8)
  - "Wage Policy and Inflation,", 1958 (Box-folder 85: 9)
  - "Wage-Push Inflation Once More,", 1969 (Box-folder 85: 10)
  - "Weitere Bemerkungen zum internationalen Währungsproblem,", 1969 (Box-folder 85: 11)
  - "Welfare and Freer Trade - A Rejoinder,", 1951 (Box-folder 85: 12)
  - "Die Wirtschaft und das internationale Währungssystem in der Zeit zwischen den beiden Weltkriegen,", 1975 (Box-folder 85: 13)
  - "Wenn der Stadt die Monopole schützt,", 1976 (Box-folder 85: 14)
  - "William Fellner,", 1983 (Box-folder 85: 15)
  - "Wirtschaftliche Entwicklung und soziale Ordnung,", 1952 (Box-folder 85: 16)
  - "Die wirtschaftlich Integration Europas,", 1957 (Box-folder 85: 17)
  - "Die Wirtschaftstheorie der Gegenwart,", 1932 (Box-folder 85: 18)
  - "Wirtschaftswachtstum und Stabilität,", 1975 (Box-folder 85: 19)
  - "With a New Look at Inflation in 1966," (Box-folder 85: 20)
  - "The World Economy: Macroeconomic Theory and Policy,", 1980 (Box-folder 85: 21)
  - "The World Economy, Money, and the Great Depression,", 1976 (Box-folder 85: 22)
  - untitled drafts, circa 1940s, 1958 (Box-folder 85: 23 - 86: 6)
  - untitled works, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 86: 7)
- Writings by Others III, 1912-1996
  - Allen, Loring, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 86: 8)
  - Annan, Noel, 1984 (Box-folder 86: 9)
  - Baldwin, Robert, 1969, 1987 (Box-folder 86: 10)
  - Baldassari, Mario, 1989 (Box-folder 86: 11)
  - Bartley, W. W., III, 1974 (Box-folder 86: 12)
  - Bauer, Georg, circa 1970s (Box-folder 86: 13)
  - Bauer, P. T., 1973-1992 (Box-folder 86: 14-15)
  - Bell, Michael W., 1993 (Box-folder 86: 16)
  - Belshaw, James P., 1959 (Box-folder 86: 17)
  - Bhagwati, Jagdish, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 87: 1-2)
  - Blanchard, Olivier, 1987 (Box-folder 87: 3)
  - Bloomfield, Arthur I., 1992 (Box-folder 87: 4)
  - Boulding, Kenneth E., 1980 (Box-folder 87: 5)
  - Böhm, Stephan, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 87: 6)
  - Bresciani-Turroni, C., 1934 (Box-folder 87: 7)
  - Brunner, Karl, 1969-1989 (Box-folder 87: 8)
  - Buchanan, James M., 1968 (Box-folder 87: 9)
  - Burns, Arthur F., 1980-1987 (Box-folder 87: 10-11)
  - Caves, Richard E., 1959 (Box-folder 87: 12)
  - Clark, Colin, circa 1970s (Box-folder 87: 13)
  - Clark, Lindley H., Jr., 1975 (Box-folder 87: 14)
  - Congdon, Tim, 1975 (Box-folder 87: 15)
  - Connoly, Michael B., circa 1970s (Box-folder 87: 16)
  - Cooper, Richard N., 1966 (Box-folder 87: 17)
  - Craver, Earlene, 1986 (Box-folder 87: 18)
  - Dornbusche, Rudiger, 1986 (Box-folder 87: 19)
  - Donges, Juergen B., 1971 (Box-folder 87: 20)
  - D'Souza, Dinesh, 1992 (Box-folder 88: 1)
  - Einaudi, Luigi, 1939 (Box-folder 88: 2)
  - Ellis, Howard S., 1968 (Box-folder 88: 3)
  - Emminger, Otmar, 1976 (Box-folder 88: 4)
  - Fabricant, Solomon, 1959 (Box-folder 88: 5)
  - Feldstein, Martin S., 1986 (Box-folder 88: 6)
  - Fellner, William, 1981 (Box-folder 88: 7)
  - Findlay, Ronald, 1987 (Box-folder 88: 8)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1925 (Box-folder 88: 9)
  - Flemming, J. S., 1934, 1953 (Box-folder 88: 10)
  - Frankel, Jeffery A., 1989 (Box-folder 88: 11)
  - Frenkel, Jacob, 1985 (Box-folder 88: 12-13)
  - Friedman, Benjamin M., 1991 (Box-folder 88: 14)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1968-1993 (Box-folder 88: 15-16)
  - Furth, John F., 1993 (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Fürth, J. Herbert, 1984 (Box-folder 88: 17)
  - Galambos, Louis, 1981 (Box-folder 88: 18)
  - Gerschenkron, Alexander, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 88: 19-20)
  - Giovannini, Alberto, 1988 (Box-folder 89: 1)
  - Goodwin, R. M., circa 1980s (Box-folder 89: 2)
  - Gordon, Robert A., 1949 (Box-folder 89: 3)
  - Graham, Benjamin, 1952 (Box-folder 89: 4)
  - Greenspan, Alan, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 89: 5)
  - Grossman, Gene M., 1987 (Box-folder 89: 6)
  - Gustafsson, Bo, 1973 (Box-folder 89: 7)
  - Hahn, Frank, 1986 (Box-folder 89: 8)
  - Hanke, Steve H., 1992 (Box-folder 89: 9)
  - Harris, Ralph, 1994 (Box-folder 89: 10)
  - Harris, Seymour E., 1948 (Box-folder 89: 11)
  - Harrod, R. F., 1934, 1958 (Box-folder 89: 12)
  - Hayek, F. A., 1926-1931, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 89: 13)
  - Henderson, David, 1990 (Box-folder 89: 14)
  - Henning, C. Randall, 1994 (Box-folder 89: 15)
  - Higonnet, Rene, 1981 (Box-folder 89: 16)
  - Hilgerdt, Folke, circa 1950s (Box-folder 89: 17)
  - Hoselitz, Bert F., 1949 (Box-folder 89: 18)
  - Hutchison, T. W., 1973 (Box-folder 89: 19)
  - Irwin, Douglas A., 1990 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - Islam, Nurul, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 90: 2)
  - Jackman, Richard, 1974 (Box-folder 90: 3)
  - Johnson, Harry G., 1964-1977 (Box-folder 90: 4-6)
  - Jonson, P. D., circa 1970s (Box-folder 90: 7)
  - Kahn, Richard, 1951-1976 (Box-folder 90: 8)
  - Kauder, Emil, 1970 (Box-folder 90: 9)
  - Kaufmann, Felix, 1934-1992 (Box-folder 90: 10 - 91: 3)
  - Kenen, Peter B., 1991 (Box-folder 91: 4)
  - Keynes, J. M., 1929 (Box-folder 91: 5)
  - Kindleberger, Charles P., 1963-1969 (Box-folder 91: 6)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., 1992 (Box-folder 91: 7)
  - Kitamura, Hiroshi, 1958 (Box-folder 91: 8)
  - Knapp, Horst, 1990 (Box-folder 91: 9)
  - Knight, Frank H., 1985 (Box-folder 91: 10)
  - Krueger, Anne O., 1990 (Box-folder 91: 11)
  - Krugman, Paul, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 91: 12-13)
  - Krüger, Simon, 1928 (Box-folder 91: 14)
  - Kulla, Bernd, 1990 (Box-folder 91: 15)
  - Kuznets, Simon, 1977 (Box-folder 91: 16)
  - Küng, Emil, 1978 (Box-folder 91: 17)
  - Lal, Deepak, 1986 (Box-folder 91: 18)
  - Lange, Oscar, 1943 (Box-folder 91: 19)
  - Lerner, Abba P., 1968 (Box-folder 91: 20)
  - Lindbeck, Assar, 1986 (Box-folder 91: 21)
  - Lindsay, Michael, 1987 (Box-folder 91: 22)
  - Lipsey, Robert E., 1987 (Box-folder 91: 23)
  - McCloskey, Donald, 1981 (Box-folder 91: 24)
  - Machlup, Fritz, 1960-1983 (Box-folder 91: 25)
  - Makin, John H., 1987 (Box-folder 91: 26-27)
  - Mankiw, N. Gregory, 1991 (Box-folder 92: 1)
  - Mann, Golo, 1989 (Box-folder 92: 2)
  - Marget, Arthur, 1921-1935 (Box-folder 91: 3-4)
  - Marko, Kurt, 1986 (Box-folder 92: 5)
  - Martin, Kingsley, 1965 (Box-folder 92: 6)
  - Mayer, Hans, circa 1920s-1930s (Box-folder 92: 7)
  - März, Eduard, 1983 (Box-folder 92: 8)
  - Meade, J. E., 1973 (Box-folder 92: 9)
  - Meadows, Edward, 1977 (Box-folder 92: 10)
  - Meier, G. M., 1958 (Box-folder 92: 11)
  - Meissner, Frank, 1979 (Box-folder 92: 12)
  - Meltzer, Allan H., circa 1990s (Box-folder 92: 13)
  - Menger, Karl, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 92: 14)
  - von Mering, Otto, 1931 (Box-folder 92: 15)
  - Moggridge, D. E., 1973 (Box-folder 92: 16)
  - Mundell, Robert A., 1965-1967 (Box-folder 92: 17)
  - Niskanen, William A., 1988 (Box-folder 92: 18)
  - Obstfeld, Maurice, 1985 (Box-folder 92: 19)
  - Ohlin, Goran, 1967 (Box-folder 92: 20)
  - Officer, Lawrence H., 1982 (Box-folder 92: 21)
  - Pacqué, K. H., 1985 (Box-folder 92: 22)
  - Patinkin, Don, 1979 (Box-folder 92: 23)
  - Polak, Jacques J., 1993 (Box-folder 93: 1)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 93: 2)
  - Popper, Karl, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 93: 3)
  - Quinton, Anthony, circa 1970s (Box-folder 93: 4)
  - Rees, Albert, circa 1930s (Box-folder 93: 5)
  - Robbins, Lionel, 1984 (Box-folder 93: 6)
  - Rockwell, Llewellyn, Jr., 1992 (Box-folder 93: 7)
  - Rothbard, Murray N., 1971 (Box-folder 93: 8)
  - Rothschild, Kurt, 1974 (Box-folder 93: 9)
  - Samuelson, Paul A., 1975-1988 (Box-folder 93: 10)
  - Sanderson, Fred H., 1958 (Box-folder 93: 11)
  - Scheide, Joachim, 1986 (Box-folder 93: 12)
  - Schmemann, Serge, 1989 (Box-folder 93: 13)
  - Schmidt, Helmut, 1987 (Box-folder 93: 14)
  - Schott, Jeffrey J., 1985 (Box-folder 93: 15)
  - Schubert, Aurel, 1991 (Box-folder 93: 16)
  - Schuetz, Alfred, 1953 (Box-folder 93: 17)
  - Schumpter, Joseph, 1912-1983 (Box-folder 93: 18-20)
  - Seidl, Christian von, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 94: 1)
  - Shenoy, B. R., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 2)
  - Skidelsky, Robert, 1979 (Box-folder 94: 3)
  - Snape, Richard H., 1988 (Box-folder 94: 4)
  - Somary, Felix, 1956 (Box-folder 94: 5)
  - Spiethoff, Arthur, 1938 (Box-folder 94: 6)
  - Stein, Herbert, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 94: 7)
  - Stern, J. P., 1975 (Box-folder 94: 8)
  - Stigler, George J., 1969 (Box-folder 94: 9)
  - Stolper, Gustav, 1950 (Box-folder 94: 10)
  - Stolper, Wolfgang, with related correspondence, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 94: 11-12)
  - Stove, D. C., circa 1970s (Box-folder 94: 13)
  - Streissler, Erich, 1964 (Box-folder 94: 14)
  - Swedberg, Richard, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 94: 15)
  - Sweeney, R. J., circa 1970s (Box-folder 94: 16-17)
  - Tietmeyer, Hans, 1992 (Box-folder 95: 1)
  - Tichy, Gunther, 1983 (Box-folder 95: 2)
  - Tobin, James, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 95: 3)
  - Trevor-Roper, Hugh, 1962 (Box-folder 95: 4)
  - Tsiang, S. C., 1977 (Box-folder 95: 5)
  - Tsuru, Shigeto, 1996 (Box-folder 95: 6)
  - Tumlir, Jan, 1985 (Box-folder 95: 7)
  - Tymieniecka, Anna-Teresa, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 8)
  - Vaupel, James W., 1970 (Box-folder 95: 9)
  - Verosta, Stephan, 1971 (Box-folder 95: 10)
  - Viner, Jacob, 1928-circa 1930s (Box-folder 95: 11)
  - Walters, Alan A., 1976 (Box-folder 95: 12)
  - Wagner-Tsukamoto, Sigmund, undated (Box-folder 95: 13)
  - Wallich, Henry C., 1978 (Box-folder 95: 14)
  - von Neumann Whitman, Marina, 1988 (Box-folder 95: 15)
  - Williamson, John, 1995 (Box-folder 95: 16)
  - Wilson, Tom, 1987 (Box-folder 95: 17)
  - Winterberger, Gerhard, 1983 (Box-folder 95: 18)
  - Zassenhaus, Herbert, 1983 (Box-folder 95: 19)
  - unidentified, 1946-1970, undated (Box-folder 95: 20)
- Printed Matter III, 1927-1994
  - Accomplishments, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 96: 1)
  - "Adolph Loos,", 1982 (Box-folder 96: 2)
  - The American Enterprise, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 96: 3-8)
  - American Enterprise Institute Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - American Enterprise Institute Press catalog of books, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 9)
  - "Das amerikanische Beschäftigungswunder: was sich daraus lernen läßt?", 1985 (Box-folder 97: 2)
  - The Annals, 1951 (Box-folder 97: 3)
  - Austria: Business & Economy, 1990 (Box-folder 97: 4)
  - Austrian Economics Newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 97: 5)
  - Austrian Information, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 97: 6)
  - "The Austrian Theory of the Trade Cycle and Other Essays,", 1978 (Box-folder 97: 7)
  - "The Broken Mirror: China After Tianamen,", 1990 (Box-folder 97: 8)
  - The Brookings Review, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 97: 9)
  - Business Review, 1990 (Box-folder 97: 10)
  - "Cannes, Life Is a Festival," pamphlet, undated (Box-folder 97: 11)
  - "Capital Movements and their Control,", 1976 (Box-folder 97: 12)
  - Cato Institute conference program, 1992 (Box-folder 97: 13)
  - The Cato Review of Business and Government, 1991 (Box-folder 101: 8)
  - The Cato Journal, 1988 (Box-folder 97: 14)
  - Cato Policy Report, 1992 (Box-folder 97: 15)
  - The Magazine of Economic Affairs, 1954, 1988 (Box-folder 97: 16)
  - "The Clinton Foreign and Defense Policies: An Early Assessment,", 1993 (Box-folder 97: 17)
  - Clipper, 1993 (Box-folder 97: 18)
  - Clippings related to the European Economy, 1988 (Box-folder 97: 19)
  - Clippings related to the Japanese economy, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 20)
  - Collection of essays on economics, undated (Box-folder 97: 21)
  - "Contemporary Economic Problems,", 1980 (Box-folder 98: 1)
  - Cosmos, 1992 (Box-folder 98: 2)
  - "The Costs of War," leaflet, 1994 (Box-folder 98: 3)
  - Deutsche Bank Studies on Economic and Monetary Problems and on Banking History, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 4)
  - "The Dollar Gap,", 1949 (Box-folder 98: 5)
  - Durell Journal of Money and Banking, 1993 (Box-folder 98: 6)
  - Economic Review, 1993 (Box-folder 98: 7)
  - Economica, 1935 (Box-folder 98: 8)
  - Economics, 1992 (Box-folder 98: 9)
  - "Europe After 1992: Three Essays,", 1991 (Box-folder 98: 10)
  - "Evolution, Welfare, and Time in Economics,", 1976 (Box-folder 98: 11)
  - "Exchange Rate Targets: Desirable or Disasterous?", 1986 (Box-folder 98: 12)
  - "Exerpt from Forthcoming World Economic Outlook,", 1992 (Box-folder 98: 13)
  - The Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond Economic Review, 1981 (Box-folder 98: 15)
  - The Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis Review, 1990 (Box-folder 98: 14)
  - The Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco Economic Review, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 16)
  - "Festschrift zum 80. Geburtstag Reinhard Kamitz,", 1987 (Box-folder 99: 1)
  - "The Foreign Trade Multiplier,", 1947 (Box-folder 99: 2)
  - General newspaper clippings, 1936-1992 (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - "Handwörterbuch der Staatswissenschaften,", 1928 (Box-folder 99: 4)
  - "Handwörterbuch der Sozial-wissenschaften,", 1954 (Box-folder 99: 5)
  - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1938 (Box-folder 99: 6)
  - "Hearings before the Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy of the Joint Economic Committee Congress of the United States,", 1970 (Box-folder 99: 7)
  - "In Rememberance of the Congress of the Mont Pèlerin Society,", 1950 (Box-folder 99: 8)
  - Index to the Economic Journal, 1934 (Box-folder 99: 9)
  - Die Industrie, 1948 (Box-folder 99: 10)
  - Das Institute für Weltwirtschaft im Spiegel des "Spiegel,", 1985 (Box-folder 99: 11)
  - The International Economy, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 99: 12-13)
  - The International Journal of Agrarian Affairs, 1961 (Box-folder 99: 14)
  - International Monetary Fund Survey, 1992 (Box-folder 99: 15)
  - The International Social Science Bulletin, 1951 (Box-folder 99: 16)
  - "An Investor's Guide to Triple-A Rated Insured Municipal Bonds", 1992 (Box-folder 100: 1)
  - "Issues '94: The Candidate's Briefing Book,", 1994 (Box-folder 100: 2)
  - Journal of Institutional and Theoretical Economics, 1989 (Box-folder 100: 3)
  - Journal of Money, Credit and Banking, 1977, 1980 (Box-folder 100: 4-5)
  - Living by His Light, 1993 (Box-folder 100: 6)
  - Lloyds Bank Review, 1976 (Box-folder 100: 7)
  - Ludwig von Mises Institute publications and promotional materials, circa 1970s-1992 (Box-folder 100: 8-9)
  - Magazin der Wirtschaft, 1928 (Box-folder 100: 10)
  - "Maintaining and Restoring Balance in International Payments,", 1966 (Box-folder 100: 11)
  - Memorandum, 1979-1981, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 100: 12)
  - "Mitteilungen des verbandes österreichischer Banken und Bankiers,", 1928 (Box-folder 100: 13)
  - The Mont Pèlerin Quarterly, 1961 (Box-folder 100: 14)
  - "Multiplier Effects of a Balanced Budget,", 1946 (Box-folder 100: 15)
  - National Review, 1992 (Box-folder 100: 16)
  - National Westminster Bank Quarterly Review, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 100: 17)
  - The New Leader, 1992 (Box-folder 101: 4)
  - The Newsletter from the International Center for Economic Growth, 1993 (Box-folder 100: 18)
  - Newspaper clippings related to Liechtenstein, 1957-1985 (Box-folder 100: 19 - 101: 1)
  - Newspaper clippings related to stocks, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 101: 2)
  - Newspaper clippings related to "Task Force,", 1968 (Box-folder 101: 3)